Guide to the Central Washington University Athletics Department, Team Sports Collection 1923-2007 (bulk 1965-1995)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Scrapbooks, XI
  - CWU Wrestling- Practice, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 130-13)
  - Cwu Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1995 (Box-folder 130-14)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1996 (Box-folder 130-15)
  - CWU Wrestling- practice, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 130-16)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1997 (Box-folder 130-17)
  - CWU Wrestling- Action Shots, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 130-18)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hal of Fame, 1998 (Box-folder 130-19)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1998 (Box-folder 130-20)
  - CWU Wrestling- Individuals photos, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 130-21)
  - CWU Wrestling- Action shots, individual Shots, 2000 (Box-folder 130-22)
  - CWU Swimming- Head shots, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 131-1)
  - CWU Swimming- Head shots, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 131-2)
  - CWU Swimming- Head shots, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131-3)
  - CWU Swimming- Action Shots, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 131-4)
  - CWU Swimming-Individual, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 131-5)
  - CWU Swimming- headshots, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 131-6)
  - CWU Swimming- Head shots, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 131-7)
  - CWU Swimming- Headshots, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 131-8)
  - CWU Swimming- Head shots, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 131-9)
  - CWU Swimming- Head shots, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 131-10)
  - CWU Swimming- Head shots, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 131-11)
  - CWU Swimming Team pictures, 1991 (Box-folder 131-11)
  - CWU Swimming- Head Shots, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 131-12)
  - Education Students, 1990 (Box-folder 132-1)
  - CWU preview week, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 132-2)
  - CWU Athletic Trainers, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 132-3)
  - CWU Athletes in the class, 1970 (Box-folder 132-4)
  - CWU Trainers and Cheerleaders, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 132-5)
  - CWU Athletics-Misc Action, Team Photos (Box-folder 132-6)
  - CWU Men's Soccer, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 133-1)
  - CWU Women's Soccer, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 133-2)
  - CWU Women's Soccer, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 133-3)
  - CWU women's Soccer, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 133-4)
  - CWU Volleyball, 1993 (Box-folder 133-5)
  - CWU Volleyball-Team Photos, Action Shots, 1994 (Box-folder 133-6)
  - CWU Volleyball, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 133-7)
  - CWU Volleyball, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 133-8)
  - CWU Baseball-Headshots, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 133-9)
  - CWU Baseball-Headshots, Action shots, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 133-10)
  - CWU Baseball-Headshots, action shots, 1999 (Box-folder 133-11)
  - CWU Softball-Action shots, headshots, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 134-1)
  - CWU Softball-Action shots, headshots, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 134-2)
  - CWU softball-Action shots, headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 134-3)
  - CWU softball-Action shots, headshots, 2002 (Box-folder 134-4)
  - CWU Track and Field- Action shots, headshots, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 134-5)
  - CWU Track and Field- Action shots, headshots, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 134-6)
  - CWU Track and Field- Action shots, headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 134-7)
  - CWU Cross-Country-Headshots, Action Shots, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 134-8)
  - CWU Cross-Country, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 134-9)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1966-1983 (Box-folder 135-1)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1984 (Box-folder 135-2)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1993 (Box-folder 135-3)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1994 (Box-folder 135-4)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1995 (Box-folder 135-5)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1996 (Box-folder 135-6)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1996 (Box-folder 135-6)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1997 (Box-folder 135-7)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1998 (Box-folder 135-8)
  - CWU Football-Team Photos, Action shots, Head shots, 1999 (Box-folder 135-9)
  - NAIA plaque, 1972 (Box-folder 136-1)
  - NAIA All Sports Plaque, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 136-2)
  - CWU Athletic Certificates, 1982 (Box-folder 137-1)
  - Signed Footballs, 1993 (Box-folder 138)
  - CWU Athletics Media Guides Football, 1950-1999 (Box-folder 139)
  - CWU Athletics Media Guides- Football, 1990-2012 (Box-folder 140)
  - CWU Athletics Media Guides-Basketball, 1942-2011 (Box-folder 141)
  - CWU Athletics Media Guides-baseball, Softball, Swimming, Field Hockey, Gymnastics, 1967-2011 (Box-folder 142)
  - CWU Tennis Stats, 1942-1971 (Box-folder 143-1)
  - CWU Football Scoresheets, 1964-1999 (Box-folder 143-2)
  - CWU Baseball, 1974-2001 (Box-folder 143-3)
  - Evergreen conference, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 143-4)
  - CWU Baseball Media guide, 1984 (Box-folder 143-5)
  - Division 1 NAIA Media Guide, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 143-6)
  - Division 1 NAIA Media Guide, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 143-7)
  - Northwest Small colleges media guide, 2006 (Box-folder 143-8)
  - CWU Athletics Strategic Planning, 2013 (Box-folder 143-9)
  - CWU Gymnastics, 1968-2013 (Box-folder 144-1)
  - CWU Field Hockey, 1978 (Box-folder 144-2)
  - Division 1 Wrap up media guide, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 144-3)
  - NWAACC Stats, 1986-1998 (Box-folder 144-4)
  - NAIA Division 1 wrap up, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 144-5)
  - Nicholson Affair, 1990 (Box-folder 144-6)
  - CWU Football scoresheets, 1991-2012 (Box-folder 144-7)
  - CWU Track and field summary, 1996 (Box-folder 144-8)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1996 (Box-folder 144-9)
  - CWU Volleyball, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 144-10)
  - CWU Swimming, 1999 (Box-folder 144-11)
  - CWU Wrestling, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 144-12)
  - CWU Athletics photos misc., 2000-2002 (Box-folder 144-13)
  - CWU Baseball box scores, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 145-1)
  - CWU Baseball box scores, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 145-2)
  - CWU Softball stats, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 145-3)
  - CWU Baseball scores, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 145-4)
  - CWU Baseball scores, 1999 (Box-folder 145-5)
  - CWU Baseball scores, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 145-6)
  - CWU Baseball scores, 2003 (Box-folder 145-7)
  - CWU baseball Stats, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 146-1)
  - CWU baseball Stats, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 146-2)
  - CWU baseball Stats, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 146-3)
  - CWU baseball Stats, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 146-4)
  - CWU baseball Stats, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 146-5)
  - CWU Softball stats, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 146-6)
  - CWU Athletics Photos Various, 1960-1996 (Box-folder 147-1)
  - CWU athletics Negatives (Box-folder 147-2)
  - CWU Track and Field meet, 1968 (Box-folder 147-3)
  - CWU Basketball misc., 1976-1996 (Box-folder 147-4)
  - CWU Cross country Stats, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 147-5)
  - CWU Cross country Stats, 1984-1996 (Box-folder 147-6)
  - Women's Basketball stats, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 147-7)
  - CWU track and field performances, 1985-2000 (Box-folder 147-8)
  - CWU Women's JV Basketball Stats, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 147-9)
  - CWU Athletics Ephemera, 1988-2011 (Box-folder 147-10)
  - Dean Nicholson Merit Award, 1989 (Box-folder 147-11)
  - GNAC, 2002 (Box-folder 147-12)
  - CWU Basketball photos, 2000 (Box-folder 147-13)
  - CWU Basketball program manual, 2003 (Box-folder 147-14)
  - CWU Athletic trainer camp, 2002 (Box-folder 147-15)
  - CWU Women's Track and field, 2002 (Box-folder 147-16)
  - CWU GNAC meeting notes, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 148-1)
  - GNAC constitution by laws, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 148-2)
  - GNAC conference manual, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 148-3)
  - GNAC conference, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 148-4)
  - GNAC conference, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 148-5)
  - GNAC conference, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 148-6)
  - CWU Football box scores, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 149-1)
  - CWU Men's cross country news releases, 1966-1983 (Box-folder 149-2)
  - CWU Football news releases, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 149-3)
  - CWU Field Hockey News releases, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 149-4)
  - CWU Volleyball News releases, 1974-1991 (Box-folder 149-5)
  - CWU Women's Tennis record book, 1930-1993 (Box-folder 149-6)
  - CWU Men's Tennis record book, 1930-1993 (Box-folder 149-7)
  - CWU Football News releases, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 149-8)
  - CWU Men's basketbal JV Stats, 1962-1994 (Box-folder 149-9)
  - CWU golf, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 149-10)
  - CWU Men's Track summary, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 149-11)
  - CWU Women's Track Summary, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 149-12)
  - CWU Women's Women's JV Basketball stats, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 149-13)
  - CWU men's JV Basketball Box scores, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 149-14)
  - CWU Men's Basketball News releases, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 149-15)
  - CWU tennis News releases, 1984-1995 (Box-folder 149-16)
  - CWU Football news Releases, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 149-17)
  - CWU Baseball News releases, 1986-1997 (Box-folder 149-18)
  - CWU Wrestling, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 150-1)
  - Division 1 News releases, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 150-2)
  - CWU Football News releases, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 150-3)
  - CWU JV softball scoresheet, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 150-4)
  - CWU Women's JV basketball Stats, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 150-5)
  - CWU Softball Boxscores, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 150-6)
  - CWU volleyball boxscores, 1983-1999 (Box-folder 150-7)
  - CWU football News releases, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 150-8)
  - D1 news releases, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 150-9)
  - CWU Men's basketball news releases, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 150-10)
  - CWU Volleyball News releases, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 150-11)
  - CWU Wrestling -Tournament, 1984-1998 (Box-folder 150-12)
  - NAIA Wrestling, 1985-1998 (Box-folder 150-13)
  - CWU Softball Boxscores, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 150-14)
  - CWU Cross country news releases, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 150-15)
  - CWU football scrapbook, 2008 (Box-folder 151-1)
  - CWU Football Vs. PLU, 12-1-1990 (Box-folder 152-1)
  - CWU Football VS. UPS, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 152-2)
  - CWU Football VS. WWU, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 152-3)
  - CWU football Vs. Linfield, 1990 (Box-folder 152-4)
  - CWU Football VS. Greenville II, 11-17-1990 (Box-folder 152-5)
  - CWU Football Vs. Whitworth, 11-03-1990 (Box-folder 152-6)
  - CWU Football vs. Westminster, 12-08-1990 (Box-folder 152-7)
  - CWU Football Vs. PLU, 1990 (Box-folder 152-8)
  - CWU Football Vs. PLU, 1991 (Box-folder 152-9)
  - CWU Footballs v. Whitworth, 10-23-1993 (Box-folder 152-10)
  - CWU Football v. PLU, 1993 (Box-folder 152-11)
  - CWU Football v. SOU, 9-25-1993 (Box-folder 152-12)
  - CWU Football v. Simon Frasier, 11-6-1993 (Box-folder 152-13)
  - CWU Football v. Linfield, 10-09-1993 (Box-folder 152-14)
  - CWU Football v. EOU, 09-08-1993 (Box-folder 152-15)
  - CWU Football vs. Lewis and Clark, 10-01-1994 (Box-folder 152-16)
  - CWU Football Vs. Whitworth, 1994 (Box-folder 152-17)
  - CWU vs. EOU, 10-17-1994 (Box-folder 152-18)
  - CWU vs. UPS, 1994 (Box-folder 152-19)
  - CWU Football vs. Linfield, 10-08-1994 (Box-folder 152-20)
  - CWU football vs. Mary ND, 12-09-1995 (Box-folder 152-21)
  - CWU Football v. PLU, 09-30-1995 (Box-folder 152-22)
  - CWU v. Hardin Simmons, 12-02-1995 (Box-folder 152-23)
  - CWU v. WWU, 10-21-1995 (Box-folder 152-24)
  - CWU v. Willamette, 09-16-1995 (Box-folder 152-25)
  - CWU v. SFU, 10-14-1995 (Box-folder 152-26)
  - CWU Football v. Willamette, 09-21-1996 (Box-folder 152-27)
  - CWU football highlights, 1996 (Box-folder 152-28)
  - CWU Football v. WOSC, 10-25-1998 (Box-folder 153-1)
  - CWU football highlights, 1998 (Box-folder 153-2)
  - CWU Football v. Willamette, 09-26-1998 (Box-folder 153-3)
  - CWU Football v. WWU, 11-07-1998 (Box-folder 153-4)
  - CWU Football v. Rocky, 11-21-1998 (Box-folder 153-5)
  - CWU Football v. SOU, 10-17-1998 (Box-folder 153-6)
  - CWU Football v. Simon Fraser, 11-13-1998 (Box-folder 153-7)
  - CWU Football v. Willamette, 09-26-1998 (Box-folder 153-8)
  - CWU Football v. Azusa, 09-19-1998 (Box-folder 153-9)
  - CWU Football v. WWU, 11-07-1998 (Box-folder 153-10)
  - CWU Football v. WOU, 10-24-1998 (Box-folder 153-11)
  - CWU v. EOU, 10-31-1998 (Box-folder 153-12)
  - CWU Football v. Azusa, 09-19-1998 (Box-folder 153-13)
  - CWU Football v. Simon Fraser, 10-03-1998 (Box-folder 153-14)
  - CWU football vs. WWU, 11-07-1998 (Box-folder 153-15)
  - CWU Football vs. WOU, 10-24-1998 (Box-folder 153-16)
  - CWU Football v. Simon Fraser, 10-03-1998 (Box-folder 153-17)
  - CWU Football vs. UC Davis, 10-10-1998 (Box-folder 153-18)
  - CWU football v. HSU, 11-14-1998 (Box-folder 153-19)
  - CWU football vs. EOU, 10-31-1999 (Box-folder 153-20)
  - CWU Football v. EWU T, 09-11-1999 (Box-folder 154-1)
  - CWU Football v. EWU W, 09-11-1999 (Box-folder 154-2)
  - CWU Football v. Carroll Coll., 09-25-1999 (Box-folder 154-3)
  - CWU Football v. UNI, 09-18-1999 (Box-folder 154-4)
  - CWU Football v. WOU T, 10-23-1999 (Box-folder 154-5)
  - CWU Football v. WOU W, 10-23-1999 (Box-folder 154-6)
  - CWU Football v. Simon Fraser, 11-13-1999 (Box-folder 154-7)
  - CWU Football v. UC Davis W, 11-16-1999 (Box-folder 154-8)
  - CWU Football v. WWU T, 10-16-1999 (Box-folder 154-9)
  - CWU Football v. WWU W, 10-16-1999 (Box-folder 154-10)
  - CWU Football v. St. Mary W, 10-02-1999 (Box-folder 154-11)
  - CWU Football v. St. Mary T, 10-02-1999 (Box-folder 154-12)
  - CWU Football v. HSU T, 10-09-1999 (Box-folder 154-13)
  - CWU Football v. HSU W, 10-09-1999 (Box-folder 154-14)
  - CWU football v. SFU, 11-11-2000 (Box-folder 155-1)
  - CWU Football v. UNH, 2000 (Box-folder 155-2)
  - CWU football v. UND, 09-02-2000 (Box-folder 155-3)
  - CWU Football v. HSU T, 10-21-2000 (Box-folder 155-4)
  - CWU Football v. ST. Mary's, 2000 (Box-folder 155-5)
  - CWU football v. V. HSU W, 10-21-2000 (Box-folder 155-6)
  - CWU football v. UCD, 11-04-2000 (Box-folder 155-7)
  - CWU footabll v. WOU, 10-28-2000 (Box-folder 155-8)
  - Hightlight, 2001 (Box-folder 156-1)
  - CWU football v. WWU W, 10-13-2001 (Box-folder 156-2)
  - CWU football v. WWU T, 10-13-2001 (Box-folder 156-3)
  - CWU Football v. Willamette T, 09-08-2001 (Box-folder 156-4)
  - CWU Football v. Willamette W, 09-08-2001 (Box-folder 156-5)
  - CWU Football v. N Haven W, 10-06-2001 (Box-folder 156-6)
  - CWU Football v. N Haven T, 10-06-2001 (Box-folder 156-7)
  - CWU Football v. UC Davis, 11-03-2001 (Box-folder 156-8)
  - CWU Football v. HSU, 10-27-2001 (Box-folder 156-9)
  - CWU Football v. ST. Mary's, 09-22-2001 (Box-folder 156-10)
  - CWU Football v. Simon Fraser, 11-10-2001 (Box-folder 156-11)
  - CWU Football v. N Dakota, 08-31-2001 (Box-folder 156-12)
  - CWU Football v. W. Montana, 10-29-2001 (Box-folder 156-13)
  - CWU Football v. WOU, 10-20-2001 (Box-folder 156-14)
  - CWU Football v. UC Davis, 11-03-2001 (Box-folder 156-15)
  - CWU football v. WWU, 10-19-2002 (Box-folder 157-1)
  - CWU Football v. North Dakota T, 09-07-2002 (Box-folder 157-2)
  - CWU Football v. New Haven, 09-28-2002 (Box-folder 157-3)
  - CWU Football v. Carroll T, 9-14-2002 (Box-folder 157-4)
  - CWU Football v Ft. Lewis W, 8-30-2002 (Box-folder 157-5)
  - CWU Football v. Montana state, 10-05-2002 (Box-folder 157-6)
  - CWU Football v. North Dakota, 09-07-2002 (Box-folder 157-7)
  - CWU Football v. HSU, 11-02-2002 (Box-folder 157-8)
  - CWU Football v Ft. Lewis T, 08-30-2002 (Box-folder 157-9)
  - CWU Football v. Carroll W, 09-14-2002 (Box-folder 157-10)
  - CWU Football v. Western New Mexico, 10-12-2002 (Box-folder 157-11)
  - CWU Football v. Humboldt State, 11-02-2002 (Box-folder 157-12)
  - CWU Football v. WSO, 10-26-2002 (Box-folder 157-13)
  - CWU Football v. St. Mary's, 09-21-2002 (Box-folder 157-14)
  - CWU Football v. Carroll, 08-29-2003 (Box-folder 158-1)
  - CWU Football v. HSU, 10-18-2003 (Box-folder 158-2)
  - CWU Football v. HSU, 10-16-2003 (Box-folder 158-3)
  - CWU Football v. WWU T, 10-04-2003 (Box-folder 158-4)
  - CWU Football v. EWU, 09-13-2003 (Box-folder 158-5)
  - CWU Football Defense v. WWU, 2003 (Box-folder 158-6)
  - CWU Football v WWU, 10-25-2003 (Box-folder 158-7)
  - CWU football at the Seattle Bowl, 2003 (Box-folder 158-8)
  - CWU Football v New Haven, 2003 (Box-folder 158-9)
  - CWU Football v UC Davis, 11-15-2003 (Box-folder 158-10)
  - CWU Football v Ft. Lewis, 10-06-2003 (Box-folder 158-11)
  - CWU football highlights, 2003 (Box-folder 158-12)
  - CWU Football v WWU W, 10-04-2003 (Box-folder 158-13)
  - CWU Football v WOU T, 11-01-2003 (Box-folder 158-14)
  - CWU Football v. WNM T, 09-20-2003 (Box-folder 158-15)
  - CWU Football v UC Davis T, 11-15-2003 (Box-folder 158-16)
  - CWU Football v WOU W, 11-01-2003 (Box-folder 158-17)
  - CWU Football v. Carroll T, 08-29-2003 (Box-folder 158-18)
  - CWU Football v. WWU, 2004 (Box-folder 159-1)
  - CWU Football v. HSU, 2004 (Box-folder 159-2)
  - CWU Football v. WOU, 2004 (Box-folder 159-3)
  - CWU Football WOU #2, 2004 (Box-folder 159-4)
  - CWU Football Highlights, 2004 (Box-folder 159-5)
  - CWU Football Highlights #2, 2004 (Box-folder 159-6)
  - CWU football v Carroll pt. 1, 2004 (Box-folder 159-7)
  - CWU football v Carroll pt 2, 2004 (Box-folder 159-8)
  - CWU Football v. WWU Cascade Cup, 2004 (Box-folder 159-9)
  - CWU football v. WOU W, 2004 (Box-folder 159-10)
  - CWU football v. EWU T, 2004 (Box-folder 159-11)
  - CWU Football v. EOU W, 2004 (Box-folder 159-12)
  - CWU Football v. WWU T, 2004 (Box-folder 159-13)
  - CWU Football v. EWU W, 2004 (Box-folder 159-14)
  - CWU Football v. HSU T, 2004 (Box-folder 159-15)
  - CWU football v. HSU T, 2004 (Box-folder 159-16)
  - CWU football v. UND, 2004 (Box-folder 159-17)
  - CWU Football v W. Montana, 2005 (Box-folder 160-1)
  - CWU football v. UNO T, 2005 (Box-folder 160-2)
  - CWU Football v. WWU T, 10-29-2005 (Box-folder 160-3)
  - CWU football v. Humboldt state T, 11-05-2005 (Box-folder 160-4)
  - CWU football v. Humboldt state T, 11-05-2005 (Box-folder 160-5)
  - CWU Football V UNO, 09-10-2005 (Box-folder 160-6)
  - CWU Football W. Montana, 09-03-2005 (Box-folder 160-7)
  - CWU Football v. EWU, 2005 (Box-folder 160-8)
  - CWU Football v. WWU, 2005 (Box-folder 160-9)
  - CWU Football v. WOU, 2005 (Box-folder 160-10)
  - CWU Football v. Washburn, 09-17-2005 (Box-folder 160-11)
  - CWU Football v. WWU W, 10-29-2005 (Box-folder 160-12)
  - CWU V Montana, 2008 (Box-folder 160-13)
  - Div II Playoff Round 2, 11-24-2007 (Box-folder 160-14)
  - CWU V Mesa, 2008 (Box-folder 160-15)
  - CWU V WWU Game 7, 2008 (Box-folder 160-16)
  - CWU V HSU Game 8, 2008 (Box-folder 160-17)
  - CWU v WOU Game 9, 2008 (Box-folder 160-18)
  - CWU V APU game 10, 2008 (Box-folder 160-19)
  - CWU V WWU Game 11, 2008 (Box-folder 160-20)
  - Women's Tennis Team Photo, 1971- (Box-folder 161-1)
  - Women's Tennis Team Photo, 1974- (Box-folder 161-2)
  - Women's Tennis Team Photo, 1975- (Box-folder 161-3)
  - Women's Tennis Team Photo, 1978- (Box-folder 161-4)
  - Women's Tennis Team Photo, 1979- (Box-folder 161-5)
  - Women's Tennis Team Photo, 1980- (Box-folder 161-6)
  - Women's Cross Country Team Photo, 1978- (Box-folder 161-7)
  - Women's Cross Country Team Photo, 1979- (Box-folder 161-8)
  - Women's Cross Country Team Photo, 1981- (Box-folder 161-9)
  - Gymnastics Team Photo, 1971- (Box-folder 161-10)
  - Gymnastics Team Photo, 1972- (Box-folder 161-11)
  - Gymnastics Team Photo, 1975- (Box-folder 161-12)
  - Gymnastics Team Photo, 1976- (Box-folder 161-13)
  - Gymnastics Team Photo, 1977- (Box-folder 161-14)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1967- (Box-folder 161-15)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1969- (Box-folder 161-16)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1970- (Box-folder 161-17)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1971- (Box-folder 161-18)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1972- (Box-folder 161-19)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1973- (Box-folder 161-20)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1974- (Box-folder 161-21)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1975- (Box-folder 161-22)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1976- (Box-folder 161-23)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1977- (Box-folder 161-24)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1979- (Box-folder 161-25)
  - Field Hockey Team, 1980- (Box-folder 161-26)
  - Field Hockey Team (Box-folder 161-27)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1966- (Box-folder 161-28)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1967- (Box-folder 161-29)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1969- (Box-folder 161-30)
  - Junion Varsity Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1970- (Box-folder 161-31)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1972- (Box-folder 161-32)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1974- (Box-folder 161-33)
  - Junion Varsity Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1975- (Box-folder 161-34)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1975- (Box-folder 161-35)
  - Junion Varsity Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1976- (Box-folder 161-36)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1976- (Box-folder 161-37)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1977- (Box-folder 161-38)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1978- (Box-folder 161-39)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 161-40)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1979- (Box-folder 161-41)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 161-42)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 161-43)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 161-44)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 161-45)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 161-46)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 161-47)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 161-48)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 161-49)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 161-50)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 161-51)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 161-52)
  - Women's Basketball Team Photo (Box-folder 161-53)
  - Corrine Farrell (Box-folder 161-54)
  - Media Guide Front Covers, Volleyball, Women's Basketball, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 162-1)
  - Volleyball Team, Action Photographs, 2002-2019 (Box-folder 162-2)
  - Volleyball Team, Action Photographs, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 162-3)
  - Volleyball Team, Action Photographs, 2012-2019 (Box-folder 162-4)
  - NCAA Division II Women's Volleyball Championship Badge, 2015- (Box-folder 162-5)
  - Women's Soccer Team, Photographs, 2001-2019 (Box-folder 162-6)
  - Women's Soccer Team, Action Photographs, 2002-2019 (Box-folder 162-7)
  - GNAC Women's Soccer Championship Participant Badge, 2013- (Box-folder 162-8)
  - Softball Team, Photographs, 2011-2019 (Box-folder 162-9)
  - Softball Team, Photographs, 2016-2019 (Box-folder 162-10)
  - Softball Team, Action Photographs, 2011-2019 (Box-folder 162-11)
  - Softball Team, Action Photographs, 2011-2019 (Box-folder 163-1)
  - Softball Team, Action Photographs, 2016-2019 (Box-folder 163-2)
  - Softball Team, Action Photographs, 2015-2019 (Box-folder 163-3)
  - Men and Women's Track and Field and Cross Country, Photographs, 2018-2019 (Box-folder 163-4)
  - Women's Rugby Team, Action Photographs, 2015-2019 (Box-folder 163-5)
  - Men's Rugby Team, Action Photographs, 2019- (Box-folder 163-6)
  - Baseball Team, Action Photographs, 2017-2018 (Box-folder 163-7)
  - Men's Basketball Team, Action Photographs, 1990-2018 (Box-folder 163-8)
  - Men's Basketball Team, Photographs, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 163-9)
  - Football Team, Photographs, 2006-2019 (Box-folder 163-10)
  - Women's Basketball Team, Action Photographs, 2006-2018 (Box-folder 163-11)
  - Women's Basketball Team, Photographs, 1998-2016 (Box-folder 163-12)
  - Women's Basketball Team, Action Photographs, 2006-2018 (Box-folder 164-1)
  - Events, Football Half time, Crowds, All Spring Sports Photographs, 1993-2019 (Box-folder 164-2)
  - Baseball and Football Media Guides, Basketball Press Releases, 1992-2009 (Box-folder 164-3)
  - Battle in Seattle, Winter Sports Schedule, Ephemera, 2005-2017 (Box-folder 164-4)
  - Women's Basketball Senior Photogrpahs, 1999-2020 (Box-folder 165-1)
  - Football Team, Photographs, 1995-2006 (Box-folder 165-2)
  - Baseball Team, Seniors Photographs, 2017- (Box-folder 165-3)
  - Men's Basketball Team Photographs, Women's Basketball Team Photographs, 1989-2007 (Box-folder 165-4)